[
    {
        "question":"Which of the following function of Number object formats a number with a specific number of digits to the right of the decimal?",
        "op1":"toExponential()",
        "op2":"toFixed()",
        "op3":"toPrecision()",
        "op4":"toLocalstring()",
        "answer":"toFixed()",
        "name":"question1"
     }
     ,
     {
         "question":"Which of the following function of String object returns a number indicating the Unicode value of the character at the given index?",
         "op1":"charAt()",
         "op2":"charCodeAt()",
         "op3":"concat()",
         "op4":"indexOf()",
         "answer":"charCodeAt()",
         "name":"question2"
     },
     {
         "question":" Which of the following function of String object creates an HTML hypertext link that requests another URL?",
         "op1":"link()",
         "op2":"sub()",
         "op3":"sup()",
         "op4":"small()",
         "answer":"link()",
         "name":"question3"
     },
     {
         "question":"Which of the following function of Array object applies a function simultaneously against two values of the array (from left-to-right) as to reduce it to a single value?",
         "op1":"pop()",
         "op2":"push()",
         "op3":"reduce()",
         "op4":"reduceRight()",
         "answer":"reduce()",
         "name":"question4"
     },
     {
         "question":"Which of the following function of Array object extracts a section of an array and returns a new array?",
         "op1":"reverse()",
         "op2":"shift()",
         "op3":"slice()",
         "op4":"some()",
         "answer":"slice()",
         "name":"question5"
     },  
     {
        "question":"Which of the following function of Number object formats a number with a specific number of digits to the right of the decimal?Which of the following function of Number object formats a number with a specific number of digits to the right of the decimal?",
        "op1":"toExponential()",
        "op2":"toFixed()",
        "op3":"toPrecision()",
        "op4":"toLocalstring()",
        "answer":"toFixed()",
        "name":"question6"
     }
     ,
     {
         "question":"Which of the following function of String object returns a number indicating the Unicode value of the character at the given index?",
         "op1":"charAt()",
         "op2":"charCodeAt()",
         "op3":"concat()",
         "op4":"indexOf()",
         "answer":"charCodeAt()",
         "name":"question7"
     },
     {
         "question":" Which of the following function of String object creates an HTML hypertext link that requests another URL?",
         "op1":"link()",
         "op2":"sub()",
         "op3":"sup()",
         "op4":"small()",
         "answer":"link()",
         "name":"question8"
        
     },
     {
         "question":"Which of the following function of Array object applies a function simultaneously against two values of the array (from left-to-right) as to reduce it to a single value?",
         "op1":"pop()",
         "op2":"push()",
         "op3":"reduce()",
         "op4":"reduceRight()",
         "answer":"reduce()",
         "name":"question9"
     }, 
      {
        "question":"Which of the following function of Number object formats a number with a specific number of digits to the right of the decimal?Which of the following function of Number object formats a number with a specific number of digits to the right of the decimal?",
        "op1":"toExponential()",
        "op2":"toFixed()",
        "op3":"toPrecision()",
        "op4":"toLocalstring()",
        "answer":"toFixed()",
        "name":"question10"
     }
     ,
     {
         "question":"Which of the following function of String object returns a number indicating the Unicode value of the character at the given index?",
         "op1":"charAt()",
         "op2":"charCodeAt()",
         "op3":"concat()",
         "op4":"indexOf()",
         "answer":"charCodeAt()",
         "name":"question11"
     },
     {
         "question":" Which of the following function of String object creates an HTML hypertext link that requests another URL?",
         "op1":"link()",
         "op2":"sub()",
         "op3":"sup()",
         "op4":"small()",
         "answer":"link()",
         "name":"question12"
     },
     {
         "question":"Which of the following function of Array object applies a function simultaneously against two values of the array (from left-to-right) as to reduce it to a single value?",
         "op1":"pop()",
         "op2":"push()",
         "op3":"reduce()",
         "op4":"reduceRight()",
         "answer":"reduce()",
         "name":"question13"
     },  {
        "question":"Which of the following function of Number object formats a number with a specific number of digits to the right of the decimal?Which of the following function of Number object formats a number with a specific number of digits to the right of the decimal?",
        "op1":"toExponential()",
        "op2":"toFixed()",
        "op3":"toPrecision()",
        "op4":"toLocalstring()",
        "answer":"toFixed()",
        "name":"question14"
     }
     ,
     {
         "question":"Which of the following function of String object returns a number indicating the Unicode value of the character at the given index?",
         "op1":"charAt()",
         "op2":"charCodeAt()",
         "op3":"concat()",
         "op4":"indexOf()",
         "answer":"charCodeAt()",
         "name":"question15"
     },
     {
         "question":" Which of the following function of String object creates an HTML hypertext link that requests another URL?",
         "op1":"link()",
         "op2":"sub()",
         "op3":"sup()",
         "op4":"small()",
         "answer":"link()",
         "name":"question16"
     },
     {
         "question":"Which of the following function of Array object applies a function simultaneously against two values of the array (from left-to-right) as to reduce it to a single value?",
         "op1":"pop()",
         "op2":"push()",
         "op3":"reduce()",
         "op4":"reduceRight()",
         "answer":"reduce()",
         "name":"question17"
     }, 
      {
        "question":"Which of the following function of Number object formats a number with a specific number of digits to the right of the decimal?Which of the following function of Number object formats a number with a specific number of digits to the right of the decimal?",
        "op1":"toExponential()",
        "op2":"toFixed()",
        "op3":"toPrecision()",
        "op4":"toLocalstring()",
        "answer":"toFixed()",
        "name":"question18"
     }
     ,
     {
         "question":"Which of the following function of String object returns a number indicating the Unicode value of the character at the given index?",
         "op1":"charAt()",
         "op2":"charCodeAt()",
         "op3":"concat()",
         "op4":"indexOf()",
         "answer":"charCodeAt()",
         "name":"question19"
     },
     {
         "question":" Which of the following function of String object creates an HTML hypertext link that requests another URL?",
         "op1":"link()",
         "op2":"sub()",
         "op3":"sup()",
         "op4":"small()",
         "answer":"link()",
         "name":"question20"
     },
     {
         "question":"Which of the following function of Array object applies a function simultaneously against two values of the array (from left-to-right) as to reduce it to a single value?",
         "op1":"pop()",
         "op2":"push()",
         "op3":"reduce()",
         "op4":"reduceRight()",
         "answer":"reduce()",
         "name":"question21"
     },
     {
         "question":"Which of the following function of Array object applies a function simultaneously against two values of the array (from left-to-right) as to reduce it to a single value?",
         "op1":"pop()",
         "op2":"push()",
         "op3":"reduce()",
         "op4":"reduceRight()",
         "answer":"reduce()",
         "name":"question22"
     }, 
     {
        "question":"Which of the following function of Number object formats a number with a specific number of digits to the right of the decimal?Which of the following function of Number object formats a number with a specific number of digits to the right of the decimal?",
        "op1":"toExponential()",
        "op2":"toFixed()",
        "op3":"toPrecision()",
        "op4":"toLocalstring()",
        "answer":"toFixed()",
        "name":"question23"
     }
     ,
     {
         "question":"Which of the following function of String object returns a number indicating the Unicode value of the character at the given index?",
         "op1":"charAt()",
         "op2":"charCodeAt()",
         "op3":"concat()",
         "op4":"indexOf()",
         "answer":"charCodeAt()",
         "name":"question24"
     },
     {
         "question":" Which of the following function of String object creates an HTML hypertext link that requests another URL?",
         "op1":"link()",
         "op2":"sub()",
         "op3":"sup()",
         "op4":"small()",
         "answer":"link()",
         "name":"question25"
     },
     {
         "question":"Which of the following function of Array object applies a function simultaneously against two values of the array (from left-to-right) as to reduce it to a single value?",
         "op1":"pop()",
         "op2":"push()",
         "op3":"reduce()",
         "op4":"reduceRight()",
         "answer":"reduce()",
         "name":"question26"
     },  {
        "question":"Which of the following function of Number object formats a number with a specific number of digits to the right of the decimal?Which of the following function of Number object formats a number with a specific number of digits to the right of the decimal?",
        "op1":"toExponential()",
        "op2":"toFixed()",
        "op3":"toPrecision()",
        "op4":"toLocalstring()",
        "answer":"toFixed()",
        "name":"question27"
     }
     ,
     {
         "question":"Which of the following function of String object returns a number indicating the Unicode value of the character at the given index?",
         "op1":"charAt()",
         "op2":"charCodeAt()",
         "op3":"concat()",
         "op4":"indexOf()",
         "answer":"charCodeAt()",
         "name":"question28"
     },
     {
         "question":" Which of the following function of String object creates an HTML hypertext link that requests another URL?",
         "op1":"link()",
         "op2":"sub()",
         "op3":"sup()",
         "op4":"small()",
         "answer":"link()",
         "name":"question29"
     },
     {
         "question":" Which of the following function of String object creates an HTML hypertext link that requests another URL?",
         "op1":"link()",
         "op2":"sub()",
         "op3":"sup()",
         "op4":"small()",
         "answer":"link()"
         ,
         "name":"question30"
     }
]